{
    "questions": [
        {
			"question" : "Which of the following is NOT a valid border-style property value?",
			"type" : "radio",
			"correct" : 2,
			"category" : "CSS",
			"answers" : [
							"dotted",
							"inset",
							"glazed",
							"solid",
							"groove"
						]
    	},
        {
			"question" : "When using media queries, which of the following is NOT a valid media type?",
			"type" : "radio",
			"correct" : 2,
			"category" : "CSS",
			"answers" : [
							"tv",
							"all",
							"voice",
							"print",
							"tty",
							"braille",
							"embossed"
						]
    	},
        {
			"question" : "How do you define a flex container and enable flex content to all its children?",
			"helper" : "The answer should be written like this <pre>attribute: value;</pre>",
			"type" : "input",
			"correct" : "display: flex;",
			"category" : "CSS"
    	},
        {
			"question" : "Which of the following is NOT a valid CSS unit?",
			"type" : "radio",
			"correct" : 3,
			"category" : "CSS",
			"answers" : [
							"ch",
							"turn",
							"px",
							"ems",
							"dpcm",
							"s",
							"hz"
						]
    	},
        {
			"question" : "What is the definition of CSS?",
			"type" : "radio",
			"correct" : 0,
			"category" : "CSS",
			"answers" : [
							"Cascading Style Sheets",
							"Computer Styled Site",
							"Composed Styling Syntax",
							"Cascading Style Syntax"
						]
    	},
        {
			"question" : "What does SVG stand for?",
			"type" : "radio",
			"correct" : 2,
			"category" : "CSS",
			"answers" : [
							"Scaled Voxel Graphics",
							"Sampled Voxel Graph",
							"Scalable Vector Graphics"
						]
    	},
    	{
			"question" : "What elements are included in a CSS Box model?",
			"helper" : "Mark all that apply",
			"type" : "checkbox",
			"category" : "CSS",
			"correct" : [0,1,2,3],
			"answers" : [
							"Margin",
							"Border",
							"Padding",
							"Content"
						]
    	},
    	{
			"question" : "What are valid values to display: attribute?",
			"helper" : "Mark all that apply",
			"type" : "checkbox",
			"category" : "CSS",
			"correct" : [0,1,2],
			"answers" : [
							"none",
							"inline",
							"flex",
							"visible"
						]
    	},
    	{
			"question" : "What are valid values to position: attribute?",
			"helper" : "Mark all that apply",
			"type" : "checkbox",
			"category" : "CSS",
			"correct" : [1,2,4],
			"answers" : [
							"top",
							"absolute",
							"flex",
							"bottom",
							"relative"
						]
    	},
    	{
			"question" : "What is CORS?",
			"type" : "radio",
			"category" : "JavaScript",
			"correct" : 0,
			"answers" : [
							"Cross-origin Resource Sharing",
							"Cross-origin Requests",
							"Cross-origin Resource Script"
						]
    	},
    	{
			"question" : "What does REST stand for?",
			"helper" : "Mark all that apply",
			"type" : "radio",
			"category" : "JavaScript",
			"correct" : 1,
			"answers" : [
							"Repeated External Shared Token",
							"Representational State Transfer",
							"Request External Script Transfer"
						]
    	},
        {
			"question" : "What will the following code output?",
			"helper" : "<pre>console.log(1 +  '2' + '2');</pre>",
			"type" : "input",
			"correct" : "122",
			"category" : "JavaScript"
    	},
    	{
			"question" : "What will the following code output?",
			"helper" : "<pre>console.log(false == '0')</pre>",
			"type" : "radio",
			"category" : "JavaScript",
			"correct" : 0,
			"answers" : [
							"true",
							"false"
						]
    	},
    	{
			"question" : "What will the following code output?",
			"helper" : "<pre>console.log(false === '0')</pre>",
			"type" : "radio",
			"category" : "JavaScript",
			"correct" : 1,
			"answers" : [
							"true",
							"false"
						]
    	},
    	{
			"question" : "Who have developed React?",
			"type" : "radio",
			"category" : "JavaScript",
			"correct" : 1,
			"answers" : [
							"Google",
							"Facebook",
							"Microsoft",
							"Dropbox"
						]
    	},
    	{
			"question" : "How can you empty the following array?",
			"helper" : "<pre>var myArray = ['a', '2', '3'];</pre>Mark all that apply",
			"type" : "checkbox",
			"category" : "JavaScript",
			"correct" : [0,2],
			"answers" : [
							"myArray.length = 0;",
							"myArray.remove",
							"myArray = []",
							"myArray = 0"
						]
    	},
    	{
			"question" : "Which fruit will we get if we use the following code?",
			"helper" : "<pre>var fruits = ['apple', 'orange', 'tomato', 'pear'];<br>console.log(fruits[2]);</pre>",
			"type" : "radio",
			"category" : "JavaScript",
			"correct" : 2,
			"answers" : [
							"apple",
							"orange",
							"tomato",
							"pear"
						]
    	},
    	{
			"question" : "Is &lt;script&gt; a selfclosing tag?",
			"type" : "radio",
			"category" : "JavaScript",
			"correct" : 1,
			"answers" : [
							"Yes",
							"No"
						]
    	},
    	{
			"question" : "What is the correct way to insert a css file in html?",
			"type" : "radio",
			"category" : "CSS",
			"correct" : 3,
			"answers" : [
							"<link style='style.css'>",
							"<link attr='stylesheet' href='style.css'>",
							"<link href='stylesheet' link='style.css'></link>",
							"<link rel='stylesheet' href='style.css'>",
							"<link rel='stylesheet' href='style.css'></link>"
						]
    	},
    	{
			"question" : "Which of the following are valid if statements?",
			"helper" : "Mark all that apply",
			"type" : "checkbox",
			"category" : "JavaScript",
			"correct" : [0,2,3],
			"answers" : [
							"if(1 == 1)",
							"if(1 = 1)",
							"if(1 == 2)",
							"if(1 == 2 | 1)"
						]
    	}
    ]
}